https://www.everit-jhon.com/

CONTACT

Phone Number:

+34 613 65 78 32

Email:

dev@everit-jhon.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/everit-jhon

Location:

Spain, Galicia

KNOWELDGE

Technologies:

JavaScript

TypeScript

React & React Native

Angular

Node.Js

Styled Components

HTML & CSS & SCSS

Tailwind CSS

MySQL

iQuery

Express.Js

Axios & HTTP Requests

Git

AWS

PHP

Python

NPM

Docker

Vite

JWT

Skills:

- </> Web & Mobile Development
- </> Agile Methodologies
- </> TDD
- </> English & Spanish Speaking
- </> Autodidact
- </> Designer Skills UI/UIX
- </> High capacity of problem solutions
- </> PhotoShop, Figma and GIMP
- </> Linux & Bash

FVFRIT JHON MOI FRO LI FDÓ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Developer with around 6 years of continuing studies. I specialize in technologies such as React, Node. Js and Angular. I have knoweldge in agile methodologies, AWS and TDD, I also has been a private web developer instructor and I am currently working in my new courses where I teach my knoweldge. I also have knoweldge in C1 english and native spanish, I'm skilled in UI/UIX Design and I am a very autodidact person with a high capacity for problem solutions.

You can visit my website where I provide detailed information about me, my skills, personal projects and technologies used:

https://www.everit-jhon.com/

EXPERIENCE

<Freelance Developer/> (2015 - 2022)

I have participated in the development of various web pages and mobile applications for a number of freelance projects.

Tech Stack:

React.JS, React Native, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.JS, MySQL, Angular, Express.Js, Styled Components, HTML, CSS, jQuery, APIS.

<Full Stack Developer/> (2020 - 2022)

I worked for a small company called NORU as a Full Stack Developer located in Quito, Ecuador, I applied various knowledge to develop and update their web application and mobile application.

Tech Stack:

React.JS, Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.JS, MySQL, Express.Js, Styled Components, HTML, CSS, jQuery, APIS.

<Software Developer Instructor/> (January, 2021 - June, 2021)

I worked as a professor in private classes for a small group about Software Development.

Tech Stack:

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, React, Angular, Node.Js, Express.Js, Databases.

EDUCATION

- </> Bachelor Education
- </> Bachelor of Computer Science (2017 2020)
- </> Education from various courses and online masters (2014 2019)
- </> Autodidact Education (2014 2022)